JON YEATMAN



JONLYEATMAN@GMAIL.COM



FLETCHER, NC



404-423-7274



GITHUB.COM/YEATMAN51



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/JON-YEATMAN



HTTPS://WWW.JONYEATMAN.COM

SUMMARY

Thorough and meticulous Business Analyst/Administrator passionate about helping businesses succeed. A former small business owner who has completed certificate programs focused on Data Analytics and Web Development. Organized problem solver with a strong technical aptitude and ability to partner with leadership, sales, marketing, support, and other important teams to maximize operations and interactions. Experience with various stages of the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) especially design, analysis, deployment, and maintenance.

EXPERIENCE

Honu Management Group

Senior Operations Coordinator, 2021 - Present

- Created an interactive dashboard and corresponding reports to improve workflow and manual documenting of inventory information
- Led a team of 4 to ensure productivity levels were met in accordance with pre-set turnaround times and internal and external customer service standards
- Prioritized projects/issues and allocated personnel to consistently meet productivity goals
- Managed projects that included maintaining issues logs, providing team performance feedback, facilitating work sessions to resolve issues, creating project work plans, and writing status reports
- Identified resources, activities, and tasks needed to produce each of the desired results
- Analyzed operation processes to create and maintain efficiencies

Phoenix Custom Printing, LLC

Founder & Director of Operations, 2018 - 2022

- Oversaw the competitive bid and negotiation process with vendors and suppliers
- · Maximized immediate turn-around by minimizing unnecessary overhead
- · Partnered with local third-party vendors to create a streamlined process for clients
- Quality relationship building with clients for trustworthy product delivery

Superior Edge Leather Works, LLC

Lead Graphic Designer, 2017 - 2019

- Consistently delivered close to 500 designs quarterly per clientele
- Optimized processes working with a variety of garments, inks, and merchandise
- Streamlined production pipeline for multi-faceted items

Army National Guard

Infantryman, 2013 - 2017

- Displayed a high level of competence and professionalism under stressful situations
- Supervised, trained, and ensured the safety and welfare of a 4-person team, maintaining a 100% safety record

EDUCATION

University of Alabama, Tuscaloosa, AL Certificate, Data Analytics, 2022 Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI Certificate, Full-Stack Development, 2021

OTHER

Technical Skills: Microsoft Office, Adobe suite, Salesforce, Relational Databases (MySQL), Tableau, AWS Quicksight, SharePoint, Advanced Microsoft Excel functions, Programming languages (Python, React, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery)

Strengths: Leadership, Project Management, Training and Instructing, Out-of-the-Box Thinking, Business Strategy, Attention to Detail, Efficiency, Data Analysis